<?xml version="1.0"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<title></title>
	<link href="http://127.0.0.1:4039/news/feed.atom" rel="self" />
	<link href="http://127.0.0.1:4039/" />
	<updated>2011-09-21T10:57:38+01:00</updated>
	<id>http://127.0.0.1:4039/</id>
	<author>
		<name>7th A Leadership team</name>
		<email>gsl@7tharochdale.org.uk</email>
	</author>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Harry Potter Weekend (Pack Holiday 2002).</title>
		<link href="http://127.0.0.1:4039//2002/06/28/pack_holiday/" />
		<updated>2002-06-28T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
		<id>http://127.0.0.1:4039//2002/06/28/pack_holiday</id>
		<description>June 28th, saw 7th A Rochdale Cub Scouts going off to Bowley campsite for the weekend. They stayed in the Lodge with pitched some tents outside. The theme for the Weekend was the tales of... [..]</description>
		<content type="html">
			&lt;p&gt;June 28th, saw 7th A Rochdale Cub Scouts going off to Bowley campsite for the weekend.
They stayed in the Lodge with pitched some tents outside. The theme for the Weekend was the tales of &quot;Harry Potter&quot;, The Pack was sorted into sixes, as called out by the famous sorting (baseball) hat. After a stroll around the campsite, and down into the valley, the Cubs went to set up for the first night, with the girls sleeping indoors, and the boys sleeping in the tents, outside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next morning, after what seemed like only two hours sleep (I suppose it might have been three), the girls were rudely awakened by the boys outside their window, shouting out and telling us they were hungry (What do we want, we want GRUB!) Once everyone was up the first activities of the day started. These were climbing, grass sledging and archery. Some of the younger girls can climb like monkeys &amp;amp; shoot arrows like Robin Hood (Akela shoots like a monkey and climbs like Robin Hood). After lunch there were bases working around potions run by Snape (Akela), charms run by me, Hedwig, and transfiguration run by Dumbledore (Mike). Then, after watching some people playing war games. It was time for the campfire sing along, without any fire, inside the sports hall. After a long night singing the girls retired to the tents, where they proceeded to scare themselves with ghost stories, until they eventually returned indoors. The next morning we played games, and carried out some challenges, until after lunch, when everyone packed up and eventually went home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every one on the Harry Potter weekend had a spell binding time, much thanks to Akela for putting on such a great Pack Holiday.&lt;/p&gt;

		</content>
	<author>
		<name>Young Leader Allyson Phillips (Hedwig)</name>
		<email>group@7tharochdale.org.uk</email>
	</author>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>2001 Halloween</title>
		<link href="http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/10/04/halloween/" />
		<updated>2001-10-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
		<id>http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/10/04/halloween</id>
		<description>All three of our sections celebrated Halloween in 2001. The Beavers held a party, &amp; later on went to see "Harry Potter" at the cinema. The Cubs made skeletons &amp; monsters, whilst the Scouts Bobbed... [..]</description>
		<content type="html">
			&lt;p&gt;All three of our sections celebrated Halloween in 2001.
The Beavers held a party, &amp;amp; later on went to see &quot;Harry Potter&quot; at the cinema.
The Cubs made skeletons &amp;amp; monsters, whilst the Scouts Bobbed for Apples, &amp;amp; made Pumpkin Heads!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/assests/gallery/images/2001/halloween/image001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pumpkins&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/assests/gallery/images/2001/halloween/image002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Apple bobbing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/assests/gallery/images/2001/halloween/image003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Apple bobbing&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/assests/gallery/images/2001/halloween/image004.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Apple bobbing&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See more in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/gallery/2001/halloween/&quot;&gt;Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

		</content>
	<author>
		<name>Mike</name>
		<email>group@7tharochdale.org.uk</email>
	</author>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Ice Skating</title>
		<link href="http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/06/04/ice_skating/" />
		<updated>2001-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
		<id>http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/06/04/ice_skating</id>
		<description>The Scouts have recently been ice-skating again, at Blackburn Arena, on or last meeting before the Easter break.
No one did a back flip onto a bum this time!
 [..]</description>
		<content type="html">
			&lt;p&gt;The Scouts have recently been ice-skating again, at Blackburn Arena, on or last meeting before the Easter break.
No one did a back flip onto a bum this time!&lt;/p&gt;

		</content>
	<author>
		<name>Mike</name>
		<email>group@7tharochdale.org.uk</email>
	</author>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>2000 Activity Weekend</title>
		<link href="http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/06/04/activity_weekend/" />
		<updated>2001-06-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
		<id>http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/06/04/activity_weekend</id>
		<description>On the first weekend of half term 7th A Scouts held an activity weekend. The team consisted of five Scouts and one Cub. It all started on the Friday at 7:15 in the evening when... [..]</description>
		<content type="html">
			&lt;p&gt;On the first weekend of half term 7th A Scouts held an activity weekend.  The team consisted of five Scouts and one Cub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It all started on the Friday at 7:15 in the evening when the flag went up for the whole weekend and not just for a few hours on a Thursday or Wednesday night. Everyone was welcomed and notices were read out.
We then had a chance to get changed. We had a game of none stop cricket and burnt off some energy. Then all the Scouts that were not staying were dismissed. Soon it was time for supper and us six all got hot chocolate &amp;amp; a biscuit, yummy!
At 11:30 it was time for bed but not sleep and most Scouts stayed awake till all hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 6:30 the next morning another Scout and I arose from our beds to do a Saturday paper round. The cooks got another hours sleep and everyone else didn't have to wake up till 7:50am.
Breakfast was later then planed because Akela fell asleep. But we finally ate and loved every spoon of porridge that we had. Once the information arrived about princess Margaret the flag was put to half-mast and we all saluted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After that we strained ourselves to get the tents from the loft and started to pitch them inside.
We did two tents per team before we could even think about lunch.
At 1:15 we departed for Blackburn arena to try ourselves at the horrors of ice-skating.
As most Scouts managed to get round for four whole hours without falling down with the exception of Akela who did a classic back flip onto the bum.
When we got back we had dinner with cake and sandwiches. Once we had destroyed that we did some test work and had a wide game cut short by a heavy breathing Scout!
We then ordered a chippy supper and settled down in the back room. We had a game of cards and our chips arrived and we got tucked in.
Then we mucked around and started tuning into radio stations and wap sites and phoning our friends to find out who won pop idol.
After all the excitement of the day we all slept like logs, only to be awaken the next morning for breakfast.
After breakfast we started a pioneering project and what started life as a message board ended life as a squirrel catcher being demonstrated by having cuddlely toys hurled at it.
At lunch we had whatever food was left. Once that was over every one went on a trust exercise. Some of the sites we saw included a Shetland pony, a burnt out car and a very muddy field.
Once we got back we swept up, tidied away our stuff and went to flag down. We were all tired, cold, wet and dirty. We all rejoiced when our parents arrived.
I can sum the whole weekend up in one word Excellent. And thanks to Mike Phillips, the GSL. We hope to have another weekend like this very soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the leaders need a big thank you for making this weekend possible and I think every one who went on the activity weekend will back me up on that.&lt;/p&gt;

		</content>
	<author>
		<name>Allyson Phillips (PL of the Wolf Patrol)</name>
		<email>group@7tharochdale.org.uk</email>
	</author>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>Annual Camp 2001</title>
		<link href="http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/06/02/annual_camp/" />
		<updated>2001-06-02T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
		<id>http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/06/02/annual_camp</id>
		<description>We went to Sandiway in Cheshire. Here are some photo's from the camp:







See more in the Gallery
 [..]</description>
		<content type="html">
			&lt;p&gt;We went to Sandiway in Cheshire. Here are some photo's from the camp:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/assests/gallery/images/2001/annual_camp/image001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Backwards cooking&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/assests/gallery/images/2001/annual_camp/image002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Raft building&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/assests/gallery/images/2001/annual_camp/image003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Raft building&quot; /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/assests/gallery/images/2001/annual_camp/image004.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Camp photo&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See more in the &lt;a href=&quot;http://127.0.0.1:4039/gallery/2001/annual_camp/&quot;&gt;Gallery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

		</content>
	<author>
		<name>Mike</name>
		<email>group@7tharochdale.org.uk</email>
	</author>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>2001 Group Annual General Meeting Report</title>
		<link href="http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/05/04/agm_report/" />
		<updated>2001-05-04T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
		<id>http://127.0.0.1:4039//2001/05/04/agm_report</id>
		<description>We recently held our annual general meeting, at our HQ, as usual. Before we started the meeting, Stephen Allen, the DC, presented another long service award, to Mrs G Foster, our Group Chairman. This is... [..]</description>
		<content type="html">
			&lt;p&gt;We recently held our annual general meeting, at our HQ, as usual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before we started the meeting, Stephen Allen, the DC, presented another long service award, to Mrs G Foster, our Group Chairman. This is yet another example of how our helpers put in many years of service to Scouting. Well-done Mrs Foster!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the reports from our three section leaders, telling the parents present what the Beavers, Cubs &amp;amp; Scouts have been getting up to over the past year, we elected our officers of the executive committee, for the next year:
* Chairman - Mrs G Foster.
* Secretary - Mr A Pemberton.
* Treasurer - Mr P Downes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike expressed his thanks to all the retiring committee, before they were re-appointed for another year!
Sadly, Mr Mills was unable to carry on as treasurer this year. Thanks anyway, you have been a big support to us all.&lt;/p&gt;

		</content>
	<author>
		<name>Mike</name>
		<email>group@7tharochdale.org.uk</email>
	</author>
	</entry>
	
	<entry>
		<title>2000 Group Annual General Meeting Report</title>
		<link href="http://127.0.0.1:4039//2000/07/11/agm_report/" />
		<updated>2000-07-11T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
		<id>http://127.0.0.1:4039//2000/07/11/agm_report</id>
		<description>7thA held their AGM at the group HQ, on Tuesday 11th July. At this meeting we had short reports from both the Cubs &amp; the Scouts, along with Mike's review of the year. Cub Scout... [..]</description>
		<content type="html">
			&lt;p&gt;7thA held their AGM at the group HQ, on Tuesday 11th July.
At this meeting we had short reports from both the Cubs &amp;amp; the Scouts, along with Mike's review of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cub Scout highlights include the following;
* Cub day - Parents took their children and they got the opportunity to take part in lots of different activities including the water slide and assaults course.
* Some of the Cubs attended Sports day and achieved their Athletes Badge.
* We entered the swimming gala for the first time in a few years, with a mixed team. The Cubs enjoyed themselves.
* A trip to Roller city was a very well attended. Cubs from all over the District took over the skating rink. They went round in groups and spent time roller skating, playing in the adventure area and having something to eat. I must thank Sam Kennedy for here help that night, and on other Cub events.
* Sixer's day was held at Balderstone School. The cubs went round several bases with a scouting theme and they had a go on the climbing wall. The Cubs that attended enjoyed this event.
* Lastly the Millennium Camp, held at Ashworth Valley. This went well as most of the Cubs who went had never camped before, it was a new experience for most of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Scout troop highlights are below;
* Both the Troop &amp;amp; the Pack attended the County &quot;North 2000,&quot; Millennium Camp, held at Ashworth Valley, over the late May bank Holiday weekend. This was one of many such camps held all over the UK.
* We held an Activity Weekend at the end of March. Based at the Club Room, quite a few of the Scouts took part, with the weekend finishing with two teams entering the &quot;Darlington Hike&quot; competition.
* The Troop held an interesting meeting at the &quot;Curtain Theatre,&quot; organised by Mr Montgomery, our thanks go to Adrian for this. Of course, we try to get out &amp;amp; about as much as possible in the warm evenings.
* Last autumn, the Troop invited the Scouts from 27/15th to join them in The Fire Safety badge course. All of the Scouts that took part completed the course, &amp;amp; gained the badge.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mike thanked the retiring committee for their help &amp;amp; support over the last year.
The new members of the committee were then elected as follows;
* Chairman - Mrs Foster.
* Treasurer - Mr Mills.
* Secretary - Mr Pemberton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Committee members;
* Mrs Hindle
* Mrs Scott
* Mr King
* Mrs Whitam
* Mrs MacKinnon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stephen Allan, from Rochdale District, called to present Long Service awards to Mrs Hindle &amp;amp; Mrs Scott.
These are for the recognition of 15 or more year's service to the movement, a very notable achievement I am sure.&lt;/p&gt;

		</content>
	<author>
		<name>Mike</name>
		<email>group@7tharochdale.org.uk</email>
	</author>
	</entry>
	
</feed>
